[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the German airline?",
   "Answer": "Lufthansa"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "In which European city can you find the home of Anne Frank?",
   "Answer": "Amsterdam"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "How many stars has the Australian flag got?",
   "Answer": "6"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "How long is the Great Wall of China?",
   "Answer": "5,500 miles"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "Who invented Ferrari?",
   "Answer": "Enzo Ferrari"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "According to the Bible, who was the first murderer?",
   "Answer": "Cain"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Which two months are named after Roman emperors?",
   "Answer": "July and August"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "In what year did Princess Diana die?",
   "Answer": "In the year 1997"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "Which famous women murderer of the 19th century was never arrested?",
   "Answer": "Jack the Ripper"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "On which mountain did Jesus take his last supper?",
   "Answer": "Golgotha or Calvary"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most fractured human bone?",
   "Answer": "Clavicle"
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most famous university of Paris?",
   "Answer": "Sorbonne"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "Which animal is on the golden Flemish flag?",
   "Answer": "Lion"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of the Indian holy river?",
   "Answer": "Ganges"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "Which South American country is named after Venice?",
   "Answer": "Venezuela"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What colour to do you get when you mix red and white?",
   "Answer": "Pink"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "What is both a French wine region and a luxury American automobile?",
   "Answer": "Cadillac"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "For which narrow sea strait is Hellespont the ancient name?",
   "Answer": "Dardanelles"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "The Chronicles of Narnia’ is a children’s book series written by which author?",
   "Answer": "C. S. Lewis"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "Which BBC children's show gardens were famously vandalised in 1983?",
   "Answer": "Blue Peter"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "The common phrase 'down and out' meaning beaten is taken from which sport?",
   "Answer": "Boxing"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "Dog, Ice and Out can all precede which five letter word?",
   "Answer": "House"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "The Chronicles of Narnia’ is a children’s book series written by which author?",
   "Answer": "C. S. Lewis"
 },
]
